Visit turkision.com for more!
Oh praise be! Praise be!
Praise be. Come on.
Come on, sons!
Come on!
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is Right!
Even the iron couldn't stand
our dikhr. Faith came alive in it
Otherwise it cannot be a weapon for Turks, brother.
Allah created iron and horses to serve us.
Thanks to Allah, we've
become His army in the world.
When our ancestors melted the iron
mountain and got out, it was a spring day.
Spring brings victory to us.
Now Newroz and Ramadan are coinciding.
We will celebrate them in
our tribe, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-Blacksmith!
Come here. Well...
Prepare this sword by Newroz.
I will cut off Imren's head with this.
-As you order, Osman Bey.
-By the way...
...increase the number of forges in the tribe.
I want a thousand swords ready by the holiday.
As you order, my Bey.
Alright. Let's go.
As Franks settled in Karacapinar, it
means the hunting season has begun, Boran.
As you said, my Bey. Our warriors
have been going after them for two days.
They built headquarters in that
area and took strict measures.
Franks are the scouts of
Crusaders. If we can't break them...
...they will join Imren. We can't let that happen.
Which measures could stand against
the sword forged with dhikr, my Bey?
We'll go to fight but they
will think we're going to hunt.
Shepherd!
-Peace be upon you
-Peace be upon you too, my Bey.
Look at these.
It's time for them to be tagged.
Tag them in a week. As you order, my Bey.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Don't run! You're losing meat by running!
Father! Father!
You never stop bragging and you're losing a fight?
Ghazi, come give us a hand.
The tribe should be ready quickly.
Hey, brother!
We're under attack!
Watch out!
Ghazi, come here!
Brother!
Praise be! Praise be!
Look at that. The tribe is good not
only for hatuns but also for lltutan.
Look at those moves!
He lies down there so good
Praise be! Wherever he
steps, he makes it a homeland!
Well, Solgur Agha. That's why.,
we call him lltutan (Homemaker).
You see, my Bey? Even
horses are happy for the spring!
When we go hunting, we'll be
happy as well, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
They are beautiful.
May your work be easy, hatuns!
-Thank you.
-Praise be. Give it to me.
Praise be!
It looks great, huh?
They are wonderful.
When they are embroidered,
their colors will look so nice.
Yes. It makes us feel refreshed, huh?
Come here!
-You are my iftar food!
-Stop running! You're fasting!
-You will sweat too much, Ghazi!
-Ghazi, isn't that my goat?
-Leave it alone! Ghazi! Ghazi!
-Well...
Come on, hatuns!
Stop, Elcim Hatun. I can carry it.
The tribe makes everyone feel refreshed.
-Osman Bey was just on point about this.
-Yes.
We really missed it. After all,
we weren't raised in the palace.
Ha? Thanks to this, you've seen our true nature.
-Actually, I want to talk to you about something.
-Go ahead, Elcim Hatun.
We haven't had the chance to
talk after... after Holofira's death.
There is nothing to talk about, Elcim
Hatun. Everything is apparent now.
I am very sorry, Orhan Bey.
I was very angry at first..
..however, I did not want anyone to die.
I know. I know, Elcim Hatun.
I saw how you tried your
best for Holofira at the court.
However, I don't want to
talk about this matter anymore.
And you shouldn't think about it anymore.
We are going on a road with
you. There will be a wedding for us.
For the good of the two
tribes, we are doing our duty.
I want your heart and your mind..
..to be at the good of our tribe.
The future of our family.
I want the same from you too, Orhan Bey.
May your heart and mind
be at the future of our family.
Thank you, Elcim Hatun.
A change of place would be good we
said, and we here we are in the tents.
Thank Allah.
The tents are good for us in Ramadan Mubarak.
They are.
If Allah permits, we will
make the wedding here as well.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
It will be a great festive.
It will be.
So, it is tradition. We need to go on a hunt.
However, this hunt will be different.
This is not an animal hunt.
It will be a hunt for crusaders.
No one will know about it.
May you prevail, my Bey.
-May you not falter.
-Thank you.
May you hunt well, Osman Bey.
Thanks. Then, let it be glorious.
Come on, valiants.
Let me go! Let me!
-Let me go!
-Come on!
Did you think Germiyanid Mehmed
Bey let you get away with this?
Alaeddin! You are dragging me everywhere
However, I promise that I will not let you have it.
Tell me! What happened?
Shut it, Mehmed Bey
Take your alps and leave my tribe.
We thought you were honest and forgave you.
Osman Bey let infidels
have the Frontier Marketplace.
He killed my soldiers. You are
making a mistake by not killing me.
If I am Germiyanid Mehmed Bey,
I will make your lives unbearable.
Here is us and our lives. Do it if you can, Mehmed.
Now, get out!
It seems your justice and mercy cannot be trusted.
They do not understand, Gonca.
From now on, our swords will speak.
My son, we cannot trust Mehmed..
..until we find out who told
Imren about Kite stronghold.
He might be the traitor.
He is mad and all, however,
he is no traitor mother.
We will see. If he is not a traitor..
...he will gather his alps
and attack Imren at once.
If he is a traitor, if he made a deal with Imren...
...then you know what to do.
I will find out who Mehmed sided with.
Alaeddin. If Mehmed betrayed us...
...then, you are allowed to kill him, my son.
It is Osman Bey's command. I know...
...your duty is difficult, however..
Osman Bey's command is above it, mother.
A traitor will always be a traitor.
What needs to be done will be done.
I'll be on my way.
Come on!
Difficult challenges await you, my
son. May Allah show you the way.
Peace be upon you, my Bey.
Peace be upon you too.
My Bey, as you have commanded, Turahan
snuck in among frenks as he saw them.
-Tell me.
-He has written their plans here.
However, they will not be alone.
Imren ordered them to unite with Catalans and walk.
They will meet up tomorrow.
Before that, a Catalan unit
will come to frank encampment.
-What about the location of Catalans?
-I still could not find it, my Bey.
Alright.
You gave me information about their plans.
Now, we will look for information
outside. Do not stay among them anymore.
-We will destroy the place at night.
-As you command, my Bey.
-Fatma Hatun.
-Was there anything suspicious?
There was a secret meeting with a
man. It was made in quite secrecy.
After that, the man passed along a letter to her.
We will see what that letter is about.
Take it over there.
Praise be to you my daughter.
You did not stop for a moment.
At this pace we'll finish
settling in two days, huh?
Thank you, I'm one of you now.
-Hah, Ulgen.
-The clothes have come, Malhun Hatun.
You arrived just in time, Ulgen.
Come on, bring them here.
Come, my daughter. Come.
The clothes for your wedding dress have arrived.
We need to start sewing them quickly.
Look, my daughter, if you
like any of these, let me know.
Look... Look at this...
This color would suit you very well, huh?
And this one's color is also
very beautiful, it would suit you.
Do you think it will be ready
for the wedding, Malhun Hatun?
There's a lot to do with the tribe and the wedding.
What should we do? Should we postpone the wedding?
We'll figure things out,
don't worry, my daughter...
...it will be ready in time,
we will manage it together.
Mother...
Mute girl came from the marketplace.
She met someone in the marketplace.
Keep an eye on her, my Fatma.
Come on. Come on, Ulgen, let's open these chests.
Let's see the things we have.
Look...
Our Alps are ready to march to
the Frankish headquarters, my Bey.
They will wait, they will wait.
We will gather intelligence around the
headquarters. Catalans and Franks are uniting.
When, my Bey? -Tomorrow.
That's why we will attack them
tonight. There is no other way.
We will quickly gather intelligence
and whatever else is needed, my Bey.
But since their main goal is Al-Quds..
...they have come with heavy weapons.
-Don't worry.
Everything is written here. We
will make all our moves accordingly.
Let them take whatever
precautions they want, my Bey.
They are in the wrong
lands, facing the wrong men.
What will Imren Tegin say to this, my Bey?
Imren will think Catalans attacked the Franks.
The Catalan vanguard is coming, we will use them.
Come on, we will get close to the
quarters. We will think about our move.
-Yes my Bey!
Come on! Come on!
Goat-smelling barbarians...
Damn it.
Look at me. I look like a servant.
I endure this disgrace to kill you all...
Andra... Fill up that bucket, pour it over these.
I will make them pay for this.
May it be easy, Olivia Hatun.
-Do you need anything?
-Thank you.
I guess Osman Bey went somewhere important.
The joy of the people could be heard from my tent.
One foot of the Turk is at the wedding...
...the other is in the hunt.
And Osman Bey went hunting.
Tell me... Have you gotten used to the tribal life?
I have.
Holofira might be guilty...
...but her death really hurt me.
Being here makes me feel good.
Holofira was in a poisonous love.
And it ended when she died.
May Allah forgive her sins.
From now on, we will look ahead.
May it be easy.
Take these to the dowry tent. They
are all heirlooms from my mother.
They are all handcraft. Place them in a good spot.
Holofira got what she deserved.
But the fire in my heart hasn't cooled down yet.
Her head should have been
taken, paraded through city after city.
She paid for what she did, why are you still angry?
Aunt...
Ayca... What are you looking at?
You don't seem well.
I am alright. I am alright.
I will be even better.
Thanks to Allah, my daughter.
You've been sleeping for days.
-Nothing bad happened, right?
-No. Our game worked.
Everyone thinks you are dead.
We were scared when it got late, but...
...but Alaeddin had already
informed us about this in advance.
You don't have any pain or ache, right?
No. I am alright.
It happened just as he said, I
haven't slept like this in a long time.
Good. Good, praise be. Holofira...
It was a dangerous game, my daughter.
You accepted without any hesitation.
I did my duty.
I hope the truth comes out soon.
I never did something like that.
-What about this ring?
-It belongs to my aunt.
There was poison in this.
Did she... Did she do this?
The evidence is pointing to her, Holofira.
But why? Why would she do this?
To prevent the union of the two Kayi tribes.
Apparently Olivia Hatun
is still serving Imren Tegin.
How could she do this?
And she did it even knowing that
everyone would blame you, Holofira.
Will you kill her? -Not now.
First, she will tell us the
names of those who help her...
...and the location of Imren
Tegin's secret passages.
She will tell us for justice to prevail. But...
...you will secure the justice.
How am I going to do this? -By dying.
No one but those in this room will know this.
We will host you in the lodge
for some time, my daughter.
Being here will be very good for me.
But... Orhan must not know that I am here.
I know. If he knows, he can't
stop himself, he'll come here.
Holofira...
-Orhan and Elcim must get married for your cause.
And I will do my duty.
I will stay away from Orhan.
When you learn the secret
passages of Abranos from my aunt...
...I will go to Constantinople.
I will disappear, Bala Hatun.
This is the best for all of us.
You're tearing out your heart with your own
hands, and not even a sound is coming out.
Loving someone is easy, falling in love is easy...
...but giving up on that love...
Not everyone can do that.
I understand that you don't
just love Orhan, my daughter.
His heart is engraved onto yours, my daughter.
Otherwise, you couldn't do this.
Know that giving
up on such a love..
..is greater than many reunions.
You are doing what suits you, your love.
Don't forget this.
I’ll go to the tribe now. If you
need anything inform Kismet.
Actually, there's something.
I want to...
...learn about Islam.
This was the condition to
get married with Orhan, right?
Do you still want it?
Not for Orhan, I want it for myself.
I'm curious about your religion and your Prophet.
Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too my Bey.
Beys, alps.
According to the latest information we got.
...our move won't be easy at
all. But with Allah's permission
...not a single Frenk will be left until tonight.
they split into three parts when
they want to defend their outpost,
so we will attack from three
sides as soon as possible.
Their outpost is from here to there.
There are infantry with shields
at the front side of their outpost.
And behind them there are speared soldiers.
They are waiting to face our horses.
In the back they have long-range archers.
Alps with steel shields will face them.
-You will be leading them, Gunduz Bey.
-Okay Osman Bey.
Boran Bey's archers will protect you from behind.
Yes, my Bey.
Their arrows will be broken
on our shields if Allah permits.
-That's for sure.
-Our alps' arrows will kill them, if Allah permits.
Only if Allah permits. Now,
At the back sides of their outpost
there are their horses to defend
a possible attack from the front.
If they see any attack from there,
they will want to run to the horses.
And infantry with swords
are waiting around the horses.
So, Orhan Bey
-My Bey.
-With your alps
you will attack from this side and destroy them.
Yes, my Bey. We will be
like storm, if Allah permits.
Alright. After we attack from both sides
we will attack from the middle
and we will ruin the army.
And we will cut the head of the Frenk leader
they will either leave our lands
or we will bury them in these lands.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
Let the darkness settle,
then we will start our move.
But first we will destroy the Frenk patrols.
So that our move can be smooth.
Before that, we will destroy
Catalans who will come to meet them.
This will be very important for our move.
My Beys, my alps, my brave boys.
The path is pretty rough, but we are also tough.
With the permission of Allah we will handle this.
-May our holy war be blessed.
-Aameen.
Come on, everybody take your places.
Gonca, you will go to Kutahya and
inform my father about the situation.
Brother, let me fight by your side.
No, you will do as I say!
When my alps come, I'll take the Frontier
Marketplace back, I'll avenge my alps!
What happened Gonca? Why are you keeping
silent? You trusted Osman Bey a lot.
He stabbed us in the back. But I knew it.
I knew Osman was not reliable.
If I'm Mehmed Bey, son of Yakup...
...I'll make Imren, Osman and
his impudent sons pay for this!
How can you do it with a few alps, brother?
Even if I'm alone, I'll take
that marketplace back Gonca.
Wow, who are you to take the marketplace, Mehmed?
And you will do it all alone, is that so?
You can only talk behind us, Mehmed.
-You can’t do anything else.
-Alaeddin!
Brother, brother.
First you killed my alps and
now you're messing with me.
Alaeddin!
-You won’t stop, right?
-Brother, don't! Alaeddin!
Alaeddin, stop!
What are you after again, Alaeddin?
You didn't kill me in the tribe...
-...but you're ambushing me in the forest, right?
-So you're determined to kill Imran...
-...and take the marketplace, is that so?
-Why?
-Are you defending Imren Tegin now, Alaeddin Bey?
I'm just curious what Mehmed
Bey will do, Gonca Hatun.
-So you're not a traitor, is that so?
-You're the traitor!
Your father is the traitor! My marketplace...
You gave my marketplace to the infidels.
I won't let Imren or you take my lands.
You're a brave man, but I wish you
could show it more often, Mehmed Bey.
Alps, lower your weapons!
Now, what I'm saying
is... It is hard for you, but...
Be patient, wait for a while,
and let's ruin Imren in the marketplace together.
-What are you saying, Alaeddin?
-Your alps are alive, Mehmed Bey.
But it seems you will not be
at ease until you see them.
Let's get there and I'll tell you all about it.
They’re coming, my Bey.
-Let them come.
Let them come.
Orhan Bey!
-My Bey!
-Come oni
-Yes, my Bey.
Alps!
-Come oni
-Yes, my Bey!
-My Bey, won't we attack? Their numbers
are equal, they are struggling in vain.
No. They should win it easily when they are equal
so they can have a chance to
win when they are outnumbered.
We will not help them.
What's the hurry, Turk?
We are here to decapitate you.
We spared you the energy.
So you will decapitate us huh?
Pray that I promised my father not to kill you.
Or it would be your head instead of your hand.
You dog.
My Shahzade, we killed them
all. We've won thanks to Allah.
Thank Allah. Alps, I will
take this dog to my father.
You gather the banners and clothes.
We will use them later.
-As you command, my Shahzade.
-Come on.
On your feet!
-Tell me, commander.
-What do you want to know?
How many Catalans are there in your encampment?
More than two thousand, for now.
Around ten thousand more is on its way.
-What is their route?
-Their route is your land.
Is that so.
Bring him back!
Now tell me, what is their route?.
They have two options. If
your land is not safe enough...
..they will meet with Olcaytu by travelling on sea.
Who says our lands are safe?
Tell me?
Cardinal and his men.
-What if they die?
-You can never touch them.
You will not see it.
I told you everything you
want. That is why I will give you..
.. a painless death in return.
-What will we do now, my Bey?
-Banners will stay with us.
After destroying Franks'
headquarters, we'll plant them there
We need to stop this crusader army. Let us leave.
Let us destroy those franks.
As you command, my Bey.
Franks have landed on the
shore. They will move soon.
They will fall under my command after
uniting with Catalans at Harmanustu.
We'll build our first headquarters
at Yakup's marketplace.
Greet the franks, be careful.
Imren Tegin. How much do you trust Osman?
I do not trust anyone but myself, Cardinal.
However, do not worry,
Osman’s leash is in my hands.
Imren Tegin, Holofira.
She is executed.
Olivia is still on her duty.
What disorder this is? She
sacrificed herself for nothing.
The letter must've reached Olivia by now.
They will learn Holofira was innocent.
Killing an innocent..
What a tragedy. It is such a tragedy that..
Orhan will hold his father
accountable for his love for Holofira.
Only love can destroy a
relationship between father and son.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
-Are you alright?
-Thank Allah, my Bey.
So it was all a trick.
So you say Osman Bey is doing a new trick.
He gave the marketplace
away to set a trap to Imren.
You still don't trust us.
Kite stronghold was attacked.
We were keeping it a secret.
The attacker is still unknown.
That is why we didn't say anything to anyone.
Mehmed Bey. I trusted you and released your alps.
-Do not make any mistake.
-Do not worry, Alaeddin Bey.
I do not attack that dog before gathering my alps.
Alright. Still, do not show your intentions.
We still don't know who Imren's spy is.
I do not host a traitor.
You stay loyal to your cause.
Gonca, you can not reach Kutayha after this.
You go back to Osman Bey's tribe.
I will gather my alps at once.
Alright, brother.
I will be waiting, Gonca Hatun
Gonca.
I wanted you to go back
because there is no other way.
Do not forget that you are engaged.
How shall I forget the fire that has
been burning inside me, brother?
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
Alaaddin was right. We need to be more careful.
Imren's spies can be anywhere.
If he finds out we'll take the market with
Kayi people, things will be harder for us.
As you order, my Bey.
I couldn't tell you the truth because...
It was a state matter, right?
I wasn't expecting otherwise, anyway.
Trickster Hatun.
I have nothing left to hide from you anymore.
Alaaddin Bey.
No need for this.
You did the right thing.
I mean it. You seem to have
forgotten but I'm telling you.
It's over.
It doesn't matter anymore..
It's over, huh?
It's over?
Fine. Shall we have the
race that you promised then?
Fine. This shall be the last race.
Only Allah can know that.
Come on.
You are my best.
Test Hatun.
Come on!
-Let's go!
NEAR FRANK HEADQUARTERS
We'll advance quickly as far as we can.
Come on.
Be quiet, alps.
Don't let your steps...
...even scare the ants.
Come on.
This is the first land I’ve taken from Turks.
For this reason, the defense should be epic.
Kanyumaz told us about
the weak spots of the market.
We're repairing them and
reinforcing the walls, Imren Tegin.
Kanyumaz... That poor man isn't around.
It means Osman's alps killed him.
Be careful. Germiyan will attempt to do something.
So be it. They can attack if they want to die.
Finish the preparations as soon as possible.
This will be the headquarters
of Franks and Catalans.
They will join Crusaders here
and march to Konya afterwards.
What about the messengers?
We'll bring them here when things settle down.
Everything is ready for my state.
Benjamin is going to bring
Franks and Catalans here.
When I get my Seljuk sings from Osman,
...nobody can stand against me.
Alllah is the greatest.
Come on, alps. Come on, alps!
-Come on.
You can pass through lands of
Turks neither today nor tomorrow!
-Allah is the greatest!
O Allah!
We've missed fighting back
to back, haven't we, brother?
Yes, brother! For sure!
We're not done yet. Stop talking and fight.
Be careful, Boran. Don't stand
like a scarecrow behind Osman Bey.
Watch his back well.
Alright, brother.
As long as there are jackals like you,
...we will always stand like
mountain chains against you.
You can't get out in these
lands and even these forests!
Today you, tomorrow all of you.
You will get out of these lands
When Imren Tegin hears about this,
he will be truly surprised, Osman Bey.
Betrayal begins where interests finish, Gunduz Bey.
You will see. Imren Tegin...
...will just ignore Catalans.
Well... Well...
My alps! My Beys!
Migrating will end one day.
Darkness will reach light one day!
I'm Osman Bey
and I will never...
...let the cruel prevail in these lands!
I swear to you!
We sweari We swear!
We swear! We swear!
My enemies should be sure of this.
As long as I breathe,
...justice will last forever, so will freedom!
Allah is the gretest!
-Allah is the gretest! Allah is the gretest!
-Allah is the gretest!
What happened here?
My Frank brother...
Catalans! Damn!
Catalans! They betrayed us!
Imren Tegin will get mad after
learning this! We are leaving!
Brother...
Brothers... Will you continue this?
I think he doesn't have the face to do it.
He will shut up with his decency.
If I speak, I will break
bones, not just hearts, brother.
That's why I am not speaking.
-Brother...
My Bey is coming.
He'll notice it.
Then we'll be in trouble. Stop fighting.
We gained a great victory, huh, Osman Bey?
No...
This is not a great victory for us.
We only broke the crusaders' pawns.
But the actual issue is the Catalans
who built a headquarters in our lands.
And messengers who are
bringing Crusaders to our lands.
We need their heads.
I don't think we can find Catalans.
How are we going to get rid of
those messengers, Osman Bey?
They are not leaving Atranos.
And we cannot besiege it again.
Wait, Gunduz Bey... Wait.
Is Imren Tegin our enemy?
Why would we besiege his castle?
Imren will think that Catalans killed the Franks.
Someone is coming, my Bey.
My Bey. Benjamin came, he saw the situation.
They will think Catalans did it.
-Yes.
This is the news we were expecting.
Catalans will now be Imren's enemies.
Tell me... Tell me now..
Who will help Imren?
There's no one left beside us
who will support him, my Bey.
Right. He will even take us to the Catalans.
We will fight together, side by side.
Now... after taking the heads of the messengers..
...neither the Pope nor the
Western states will support Imren.
This way, the Crusader army will
stop before it even makes a move.
Otherwise...
...Imren will attack like a mad dog.
Then Kite and the tribes will be targeted.
That's why, Gunduz Bey, the protection
of these lands is your responsibility.
Come on now Alps, valiants.
We are going to Atranos.
So... Let's help Imren Tegin, huh?
Imren... Come on.
Gonca... Are you really going to
marry that man who you don't know?
I have to, Fatma.
I just have to.
You don't. You don’t, Gonca. There must be a way
Alaeddin Bey.
-What are you doing here?
-I am tired.
You can continue. -Fatma.
What do you want?
Trickster Hatun. I...
I said it's over, Alaeddin Bey. It's over.
Don't force it anymore. Come on. Please go.
Gonca... Listen to me first.
I know I hurt you today. But...
...am new to this love.
Tell me... What should I do? How
can I make you forgive me, huh?
You’ve hurt me many times, Alaeddin. But I
got used to being the one who is not trusted.
I am not mad at you. I am not mad at your family.
Our families will never
be able to trust each other.
-That’s not true.
-That's true.
We lost each other's trust.
-Don't my rose. -Alaeddin...
-Don’t, Gonca.
-Alaeddin.
No matter what you say, that's the truth.
What can we do?
This is the end of our fairy tale.
-Don't.
Alaeddin... Don't!
I promised someone.
You were not the one who promised, Gonca.
-My father's promise...
...is my promise.
Like your brother Orhan Bey...
...have to do this.
Don't go. -Safely.
Gonca! Wait.
I had this made for you.
I am telling you that I am engaged.
Please, don't do this. Please.
Then let it be a remembrance.
May you smile every time you
look in this mirror, Coy Hatun.
What do you think you’re doing?
-Gonca is betrothed.
-Mother.
-I’m in pain, I don't know what I'm doing.
-Alaeddin.
Gonca is right.
Don't cross her path.
It is a dangerous path, son.
-This path would make Turkmens kill each other.
-Don't do it mother.
-Don't do it.
-What, Alaeddin?
You will seal your heart like your brother, got it?
You have no choice.
My Allah, give me strength.
Give me strength, my Allah.
Imren Tegin.
What happened, why is your face like that?
-Where are the Franks?
-They are dead.
-Catalans attacked them.
-Catalans?
Why would they attack? Why
would they stab us in the back?
Oh my God. What are we going to do now?
This attack will wound The Crusaders’ unity.
We have to be strong. If not,
neither Olcaytu nor Pope will trust us.
Then my dream of a state in Quds
would be gone. I can't let this happen.
We will destroy Catalans before
Turks hear about this treason.
Send your men to find the traces of Catalans.
Imren Tegin. Osman is coming
to the castle with his men.
Osman?
-Did he hear about the treason?
-I don't trust Osman at all.
He will take credit for this treason.
His credit will be death sooner or later, Cardinal.
Let's see what Osman wants.
Where are you Imren?
Where are you? Show yourself!
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Did you kill my men around Taspinar?
Who else but you would draw
sword against me in these lands?
Why would I kill the soldiers of my ally?
What about those dastards you brought with you?
Do you keep those dogs on a tight leash?
Their teeth touched my soldiers.
There are some people, Osman Bey.
Who?
Catalans.
Why would...
...Catalans be against you?
They killed the Frank
units first, they destroyed
the warriors that are very
important to Crusaders.
They damaged the Crusade a lot.
I'll destroy them.
Look at me.
You invited Catalans to these lands.
If something happens, I'll make you pay for it.
If you become my ally, you
will not hide anything from me.
It is too dangerous to move
while Catalans are rebelling.
What happened, Cardinal?
You were brave enough when
you came here to declare war?
Now you started to talk when
it is about your own soldiers.
What happened?
You started hesitating when
the sword is on your neck.
If Catalans are changing sides, very well then.
We'll fight together.
Then these Crusaders will leave my lands.
We will crush the rebels together.
When I find the traces of Catalans I'll
inform you about the time and place.
Find me the den of those dogs.
We will fight by your side.
I wish you chose Christianity
and joined us, Osman Bey.
If you want this to be a long-lasting alliance,
then you will need to convert to Islam.
You will be the soldier of The Creator,
otherwise it will be over with this thing.
You're inviting me to Islam in
the middle of Crusader army.
Even if we are alone, our voices
are loud. What about the Crusaders?
What are they?
Then let's do it your way.
You will keep your religion, and I will keep mine.
Then it will be as we agreed on.
Until one of us dies, Osman Bey.
Until one of us dies.
Come on.
It's from Imren Tegin. It's very confidential.
What's going on in the tribe?
I don't know about anything.
They're working for Orhan and Elcim's marriage.
They don't talk about it openly.
Kill the spy. Blame her for Holofira's crime.
Orhan will be Osman's enemy when he realizes
that Holofira was killed as an innocent.
Hide the other letter on the spy.
It should be good news since you're smiling.
One more person will die in the tribe.
Who?
You.
-May it be easy, hatuns.
-Thank you Malhun Hatun.
Welcome, you did well.
It looks great, Ulgen.
Try it so we can make the necessary adjustments.
-Let’s give it a try.
-Hold it like this.
Right, let's see it on you.
It looks great, thank you.
Hold it as well.
You look great, daughter.
-Da you like it?
-Mother!
Mother, mother.
-What happened, daughter?
-Hilal.
She went Olivia Hatun's tent. Alps
said it, but she went there secretly
She tried to trick them to get there.
There's something wrong with this, come on.
Murderer! Murderer!
She tried to kill me! Murderer!
-Murderer!
-My lady!
-Help!
-Olivia!
Olivia, what happened?
She got in the tent and attacked me!
Told me Imren Tegin won't leave me alive!
That it is my
turn after Holofira.
I almost got killed. I killed her.
Ladies, take Lal out of the
tent, we will search her, come on!
So you say it was Lal who poisoned Elcim.
I told you. I told you all!
Holofira wouldn't do such a thing!
She died for nothing.
Was Holofira innocent?
Did we do her wrong?
My niece has died because of Imren Tegin's tricks.
Then why did she take the blame?
Why?
Why do you think? To save me!
She knew you would blame me!
She sacrificed herself! The
love-sickness had already killed her!
She was Innocenti Innocent!
Osman Bey is coming!
-Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you. May your feast be plenty.
Enjoy, come on alps.
May your feast be plenty.
Enjoy.
Thanks, thanks.
May you prosper.
-Welcome, Osman Bey.
-I feel welcomed.
-Praise be, you look well.
-Yes.
I hope you brought good news, my Bey.
We did indeed. Let us go to
the hall, I've things to tell you.
This hunt must be important.
-Looking at how joyful they seem.
-This is not a hunt.
There is something elsfe. I will learn for sure.
However, the important thing
is learning Osman's trust now.
-How will we do that, my Lady?
-I've already started, Andra.
The death of Lal will be the proof of my innocence.
My Bey, this was found on Lal.
She was with Imren Tegin, however,
we think she was also with Olivia.
Kill Olivia after Holofira.
Whoever stands against
Imren Tegin will pay the price.
So she killed Lal to shut her up.
Their intention was to
disrupt our union from the start.
She did not hesitate sacrificing Holofira.
They do not. However..
..they will pay for what
they've done to Holofira and us.
It seems Lal was sending
letters to Olivia and Imren.
Now, Lal is dead. She can
not message Imren anymore.
Imren will surely send her a letter, my Bey.
-Alaeddin.
-My Bey.
You will tell those who
follow Olivia to be careful.
Olivia will open the doors of Abranos to us.
-As you command, my Bey.
-Bala, Malhun.
You will earn her trust.
As long as she trusts you,
she will surely message Imren.
As you command, my Bey.
Are you sure you want to fight alongside Osman?
I will not waste the rest of my
soldiers to get rid of Catalans, Cardinal.
Don't worry. I will use Osman as a bridge.
Imren Tegin. The location-of
Catalans has been found.
-Where are those dogs?
They are settled near Karanlikdere.
They are being prepared to depart.
So they are being prepared.
Inform Osman at once. We
will hunt Catalans tomorrow.
This is from my Bey’s own pouch.
They will be given to those in need.
Be sure that no one will be left aided.
And no one must know these
supplies came from Osman Bey.
As you command, my,Bey.
-Oguz.
-My Bey.
Come here, brother.
You will go to each merchant.
You will find out who owes to who and pay them all.
Take this.
-If someone asks who are you..
-I am no one, my Bey.
-Come on.
-As you command, my Bey.
Come on.
-Boran Bey.
-My brother.
Why don't you play us a
song while waiting for iftar..
..so that our hearts may find joy?
Of course, my brother. Come on then.
Come on, brothers.
In the name of Allah
I found myself in the sea of Muhammed love.
That is why I am in love with Muhammed.
I found myself in the sea of Muhammed love
The one who is in the community
of the prophet will always be thankful
So, turn me into a lover of Mohammed, my Allah.
Allah put the love of Muhammed in my heart.
I found myself in the sea of Muhammed love
That is why I am in love with Muhammed.
Like Mecnun, I'd pierce
through mountains for my love
Drive me mad in love like Muhammed
He was always faithful, not cheeky.
You're the reason why Muhammed was thankful
I found myself in the sea of Muhammed love
That is why I am in love with Muhammed.
He valued his community all the time.
He is the one whose path can save you in doomsday.
I'm in deep tight love, my Allah
Fulfill my heart like Muhammed
I found myself in the sea of Muhammed love
That is why I am in love with Muhammed.
Hero with a darkened face he was.
Wish I could see him even for a moment.
Everybody is desiring to meet him.
When am I going to be honoured to see him?
I found myself in the sea of Muhammed love
That is why I am in love with Muhammed.
-Thank you, Boran Bey.
-Eyvallah, brother.
I see what’s going to happen, Scholar.
Your family will never trust me as before.
I know this. And so...
... accepting marrying a man whom I don't love.
You're also marrying a man whom
you don't love and who may not love you?
Ha, Gonca Hatun?
Whoever you see in this tribe, they want
to be a daughter or a son of Bey, right?
But they don't know about the
burden that title put on our shoulders.
You're right. Our fates are the same.
They aren't the same, Elcim Hatun.
You know the man you're going to marry.
But I have no idea about him.
And... And..
You love someone else.
Then your fate resembles Orhan Bey's.
Talking about this would only
tire our hearts, Elcim Hatun.
-Let me help you.
-They say Holofira was your friend.
Maybe you're angry with me that
I accepted marrying Orhan Bey.
No, Elcim. I know why you two are getting married.
What I'm angry with is that
Holofira got blamed wrongly.
-She was like my sister.
-I didn't want this to happen.
I know you didn't. I heard
what happened in the court.
Let's go. We shouldn't be late for iftar.
Come on.
Lots of stone walls,
..vast gardens and rooms decorated with silk, huh?
No, none of these would please
me as much as this tent, Osman.
You're right, Bala.
I’m glad we came to the
tribe. Everyone is so happy.
Well, Bala... The., plane tree is growing.
Its branches are growing high to the sky.
But the leaves want to reach the
roots. We are something like that.
We had the greatest joys in this tribe.
My first love. My first test.
My first victory.
My first defeat.
I had all of these here.
I want my children to bury their suffering in
this land and cry out their joys to this sky.
-Our children, huh?
-Yes.
They grow up so fast. When I look at them,
...see your mercy in Fatma,
your wisdom in Alaaddin...
...and your strength in Orhan.
They're going through many
hardships for our cause as well.
I know you see that.
I do. Holofira?
-Did you see her? Is she alright?
-She's good.
Trying to stay strong. But the pain in her eyes...
-It's so obvious there.
-Just like Orhan.
I know, Bala. I know about this.
I know Orhan and Alaaddin.
Lovers have different eyes but the same looks.
And our struggle is a garden of roses.
The rose is a gift but the thorn is a hardship.
But our cause will grow bigger
as we endure these hardships.
We endured these hardships, now
our children are...
-And then their children will.
-If Allah permits.
May Allah relieve their hearts
and make their hardships easy.
Aameen. Aameen.
May Allah keep our children
and family in the right path.
-Aameen.
-Come on.
Everyone is waiting for us to join iftar. Let's go.
It looks so nice.
Who knows how delicious it is?
Allah! Mother! When is the azan?
Very soon. Come on.
Ghazi, stop smelling.
It might break your fast.
Soon we will meet.
What was that?
Is it coming from your
stomach? Are you that hungry?
Yes, it's coming from my stomach.
"Give me food", it cries!
-Give me food;
He's just like your father! My boy!
Couldn't he find anything else to take from you?
It looks yummy! My Allah! Thank You for Your gifts!
My favorite. From the fattiest part!
Father.
You're my father but this
bulgur with meat is my right!
My mother made it for me!
Is this how you respect your father?
Stop playing over it!
Cerkutay, stop acting childish
-Is that Gonca Hatun?
-Gonca Hatun?
-You lost due your weakness, son.
-Oh?
He should have no weaknesses?
Give that plate to the kid.
What should I do?
Shall I starve to death?
I would never leave you hungry.
-The meatiest part is yours.
-My hatun...
My hatun... Ghazi, you know what?
Your mother is the best.
-I can never do that to you.
-My hatun...
I made this for you.
-You're beautiful.
Mother. If you
wait a bit longer,
...alps will have iftar with water.
He's right.
My Bey.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the compassionate.
Thank you, mother.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the compassionate
May Allah accept our fasting.
-Aameen.
Aameen.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the compassionate
Here. Thank you.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the compassionate
InshaAllah our gaza will be accepted, my Bey.
On this blessed day, while the
Crusaders are coming upon us...
...you become a shield for the oppressed.
Whoever holds the banner would have done the same.
We have destroyed the Franks. Now...
...now, it is the turn of the Catalan leader.
Imren fell into the trap,
my Bey. When he reveals
the location, this matter
will be over, InshaAllah.
The Crusaders will know that only
death awaits them in these lands, brother.
Look at them... They turn into
lions when talking about war.
O Praise be to my valiants.
My Bey... My brothers can
sacrifice anything for this.
We are doing our duty, sister.
What about the Cardinal and messengers, my Bey?
-After destroying the Catalans...
...we will find a solution for that.
In the end, it will be Imren Tegin's turn.
The victory will be Osman Bey's again, right?
Victory will always belong to Islam.
Aykurt... You were saying
something, come on, say it.
You are right, Solgur Agha.
Brothers... You were not there, but...
...Cerkutay Bey is my witness. I faced an infidel.
He was giant. What did your Aykurt brother do?
He drew his sword...
...he lowered his sword in such a way that...
Well, what happened, Aykurt?
-Then...
... split the infidel in half like an apple.
Brother, slow down, it is not an apple.
Oh praise be! My Aykurt
struck with the power of faith.
Or else, which sword splits a man in half?
Believe it or not.
That was the story.
-We believe you, Aykurt brother...
...we believe you. Why wouldn't we
believe? Isn’t that right, Solgur Agha?
Sorry, if I don't see it, I don't believe it.
I'm leaving the table then!
Wait, give sherbet, give sherbet.
Give sherbet.
That's what happened.
Tonight you fulfilled a great duty,
Alps, the infidels were defeated...
...thanks to all of you. But the war will continue.
From now on, we will be even more cautious.
A mistake we make during battle
can lead us to the edge of a hill.
Isn't that right, Boran?
I don't know if you are talking to me, Konur.
But I always fulfill my duty
properly, let no one doubt that.
You do it properly, but today, Osman
-Bey almost died because of you.
What do you say to that?
I've been so curious since
I started talking to you.
You accept Jesus as a Prophet...
...but believe in Islam.
I mean the prophecy of Muhammad.
Dervish Efendi, tell me. How doe his happen?
Not only him, but Allah has sent dozens of...
...prophets since Hadhrat Adam.
We believe each of them, according to our faith.
But we believe that Hadhrat
Muhammad is the last prophet.
So, did Muhammad, your Prophet...
...also face difficulties like Jesus?
What was he like?
His journey...
The difficulties and tests
began before he was born..
What was he like, you ask.
I will tell you, sure. He was
called Muhammad-ul Amin...
...even before nubuwwah. Do you know why?
He does not betray trusts, he does not lie...
...and he is fair.
Have you heard about the Kaaba?
Your pilgrimage place.
The two prominent tribes of
Mecca had a dispute about placing...
...the Black Stone in the Kaaba.
One said, "We are the noblest tribe of Mecca.
It suits us to place the
stone." The others objected...
"We will not let this happen." they said. They...
...almost came to the point
of strangling each other.
At that moment, Hadhrat Muhammad came.
They said, "Let's ask
Muhammad, let him decide for us.
Let him decide who will place the Black Stone.
He will secure the justice." The
Messenger of Allah accepted it.
He took off his blessed
cloak and put it on the ground.
He placed the Black Stone on it.
He made the leader of one
tribe hold one end of the cloak...
...and the leader of the other tribe the other end.
Thus, he resolved the
dispute between the two tribes.
It is a beautiful story.
I've told you just a drop from the ocean.
There is much more, but our words are not enough.
My son... -My Bey... -Sit down.
What's that? You've brought the
stars down by watching them, huh? ..
I am watching them. But am I seeing it?
That's doubtful, father.
-So are you saying that you can't differentiate...
...between the day and night?
-Not at all, my Bey.
Our cause does not allow blindness.
Above all, you taught us this.
Shahzade Orhan. My son.
You are hiding the distress you are suffering.
Your father knows everything, my son. Everything.
You gave up your love for our cause.
I did what I had to do for my duty my Bey.
I have no complaint, and I can never complain.
Besides, when everything is revealed,
Holofira will go to Constantinople.
I won't be able to see her again.
My son... My son...
-But you mentioned the stars, my Bey...
When night falls, looking at the starry sky...
...feels like looking at her face.
That's why I get lost in it like that.
Look...
You will live whatever is in your fate.
If it is destined for you to
experience this love again...
...then Holofira will surely return to you.
What if it's not, my Bey?
Also
What happens if Holofira and I cross paths again?
I'll have another family with someone else.
My Bey, we buried our love for our cause.
There's nothing important
than the future of our Beylik.
The teravih time is soon.
Let's go and perform ablution.
Come on.
How did she trick me?
We thought she was a wounded
gazelle, but she turned out to be a snake.
She was a snake but she got
what she deserved, thankfully.
Now it's time to cut the head of the snake.
Then she must be the one who poisoned Ayca.
Maybe it was all a game.
Maybe Olivia used her and she
killed her when she is done with her.
Maybe both of them were working with Imren.
So Holofira died in vain, is that so, Bala Hatun?
Why did Holofira accept the crime
and risked death if she was innocent?
It seems they played tricks
on Holofira, Elcim Hatun.
But even though you all knew her, you blamed her.
She wouldn't have taken
the blame. They're all guilty.
Maybe Hilal was working for her?
-Holofira is an infidel, Gonca Hatun.
-If Holofira
had told us the truth, we would have helped her.
Gonca daughter. But she pleaded guilty.
If you had believed her,
maybe she would have told you.
But you put pressure on her.
It seems you left Holofira no other chance.
She pleaded guilty because she was guilty.
She got what she deserved.
That snake-tongued girl tricked you.
Sister-in-law, it's not proper
for us to speak ill of the dead.
She was a murderer, how should I talk about her?
Holofira was not a murderer Ayca Hatun.
-She was innocent.
-She was innocent, is that so?
That girl was a bloody murderer.
She tricked you all.
But I told you. That girl brought
trouble and blood to this house.
-This blood cannot be cleaned.
-Enough, Ayca.
Shut up now.
There will be blood.
They are blind.
Only you can see the truth.
You're still defending the dead.
But she shed the first blood in
the palace. She tried to kill me.
-That's enough.
No.
-It's not enough.
-Sister in law.
The wedding will be bloody.
There will be bloodshed.
Forgive me.
This poison turned her into someone else.
Think before you talk, Konur,
I always protect Osman Bey.
I never hesitate to put myself at risk.
You can only talk. If I didn't get there
on time, Osman Bey would be dead now.
Be careful! Talk carefully.
You're the one who can only talk.
You keep making mistakes. Tell me,
wasn't Kite outpost under your command?
How did they attack the hidden
outpost? Why didn't you take precautions?
Boran Bey, what kind of blame is
this? We were also in the Kite outpost.
-We took proper precautions.
-Aykurt brother,
while Beys are talking
-it’s not our place to talk,
said what I had to say, Aykurt.
Understand the rest as you wish.
Boran, you say that Kite outpost was attacked
but you didn't say a word
when its place was discovered.
What your spies were doing
when Imren attacked the outpost?
Were they looking around idly?
Brothers, brothers, what are you doing?
What are you doing brothers?
Don't do it. Our fight is with the
infidels and our wrath is towards them.
Everyone knows it.
Boran brother values Osman
Bey's life more than his own life.
Konur Bey is known for his
order and his love for his alps.
Don't do it brothers. It doesn't suit us.
I kept my silence until now just
because it doesn't suit us, brother.
But those who joined Osman Bey on the road
equate themselves to those who set out with him.
I've protected Osman Bey from the beginning.
Let me tell you, my Bey doesn't carry
the wound I opened on his back, Konur.
Boran, Boran.
If you knew yourself well, you wouldn't
have mentioned about the old incidents.
If you had done your
duty properly then, Osman
Bey wouldn’t have that
wound on his back today.
Boran, Boran!
-Let go off me!
-Boran!
I wish you were so tough on
the field while protecting my Bey.
I'll ruin you!
What did you do, brothers?
Baysungur
-Boran! Boran! What did you do?
-Let go off me!
-Alps!
-Osman Bey is coming.
What’s going on here?
Huh?
What's this situation? What happened here?
Are you shedding each other's blood?
Answer me!
And you keep your head
down? Look as angry as before!
You're the alps of Kayi! Does it suit you?
-My Bey.
-Shut up!
Nothing is enough to explain this.
Tell me. Tell me what was the problem.
What was the problem between you?
You even let alps join the fight.
Is it terrible that you came to the tribe?
Did you feel bad about it? Did
you want to show your bravery?
If that's the case, you'll do it on the field!
There is no self in our cause.
You can never turn your back to each
other while you are fighting side by side!
You were conquering castles
with thousands of men behind you.
You were shaking the
battlefields, what happened now?
Did you lose your temper with each other?
If you do this
you will drag everyone behind you into the abyss.
I would never let something like
that happen to the army of Kayi.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Take their swords.
There will be a court tomorrow.
Whatever your judgment is, you will abide.
-Yes, my Bey.
-Take their swords.
Take them to the dungeon.
Shame on you.
Now get lost.
Visit turkision.com for more!